<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright 2014 Jay Soyer
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
	<!--About Screen - About Heading-->
	<string name="info_about_title">About</string>
	<string name="info_about_message">
		\t\tInitially created as a way to test the Advanced-Adapters library, this app now serves as a
		demonstration of all available adapters and their associating features found within it. The
		Advanced-Adapters library spawned out of frustration in having to constantly re-write a new
		adapter for various apps I\'ve worked on over the years. Needing a custom solution proved far
		more common then needing the generic ArrayAdapter provided by Android. While their version
		serves a basic generic purpose, it\'s filtering inconsistencies/bugs became a pain to deal
		with, ultimately requiring me to re-write their adapter any time I wanted to support
		filtering.
	</string>
	<string name="info_about_url">https://github.com/JaySoyer/Advanced-Adapters</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - Android's ArrayAdapter-->
	<string name="info_android_arrayadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_android_arrayadapter_message">
		The following is a demonstration of Android\'s ArrayAdapter in action to show just how easy
		it is to break.  Mostly the problems revolve around the filter. Try doing this:\n
		\n
		\t - Perform a search\n
		\t - Close the search view\n
		\t - Attempt to add a new movie\n
		\t - Behold…nothing is added.\n
		\t - Demo is now in a bad state.\n
		\t - Hit back and re-enter demo.\n
		\t - You\'re back in a good state.\n
		\n
		As soon as the ArrayAdapter performs one search, the adapter can longer be
		mutated without seeing problems. Can you find any other problems? Head on over to the wiki
		to find out more issues.\n\n
	</string>
	<string name="info_android_arrayAdapter_url">https://github.com/JaySoyer/Advanced-Adapters/wiki/</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - Android's SimpleExpandableListAdapter-->
	<string name="info_android_simpleexpandable_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_android_simpleexpandable_message">
		The following is a demonstration of Android\'s SimpleExpanadableListAdapter in action. While
		there are no bugs with the adapter, it is severely lacking in functionality, usability, and
		easability. Yes despite the name, it\'s a pain to convert your data for it. Just check out
		the source code.\n
		\n
		After playing around here, check out the Rolodex Adapter demos. Far more capable and easier
		solutions to use.
	</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - AbsArrayAdapter-->
	<string name="info_absarrayadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_absarrayadapter_message">
		This is a demonstration of the AbsArrayAdapter, which is an adapter backed by an ArrayList.
		This adapter is an improved version of Android\'s ArrayAdapter, resolving many of it\'s
		issues. Most notably, all the filtering problems.\n
		\n
		If filtering is not required, it\'s strongly recommended to use the NFArrayAdapter instead.
	</string>

	<!--About Screen - Credits Heading-->
	<string name="info_credits_title">Credits</string>
	<string name="info_credits_message_library">
		\t\tThough heavily modified, Android\'s ArrayAdapter served as the foundational code for
		the Advanced-Adapters library.
	</string>
	<string name="info_credits_message_android_url">https://source.android.com/license.html</string>
	<string name="info_credits_message_demo">
		The following was used to help build the Advanced-Adapters Demo app:
	</string>
	<string name="info_credits_message_retain_url">http://thenounproject.com/term/crop/11553</string>
	<string name="info_credits_message_plug_url">http://thenounproject.com/term/plug/33432</string>

	<!-- Info Dialog - JSONAdapter -->
	<string name="info_jsonadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_jsonadapter_message">
		This is a demonstration of the JSONAdapter class, which is a full fledged adapter backed by
		a JSONArray.  Keep in mind, JSONArray is not part of a Collection and does not behave like a
		normal array.  It\'s ability to dynamically change the underlying data is very limited but
		possible.\n
		\n
		This adapter specifically supports a highly customizable filtering process which allows easy
		support for whatever data type is stored within. If filtering is not required, it\'s
		strongly recommended to use the NFJSONAdapter instead.
	</string>

	<!--About Screen - License Heading-->
	<string name="info_license_title">License</string>
	<string name="info_license_message">
		\t\tThis demo app and the Advanced-Adapters library are both under the Apache License v2.0.
		You may not use either app or library except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
		a copy of the License at:
	</string>
	<string name="info_license_url">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - NFArrayAdapter-->
	<string name="info_nfarrayadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_nfarrayadapter_message">
		This is a demonstration of the NFArrayAdapter class, which is an adapter backed by
		an ArrayList.  This adapter is an improved version of Android\'s ArrayAdapter but removes
		filtering support.  As a result, there is no need for synchronized blocks which may help
		those worried about performance.\n
 		\n
 		If filtering is required, it\'s strongly recommended to use the AbsArrayAdapter instead.
	</string>

	<!-- Info Dialog - NFJSONArrayAdapter -->
	<string name="info_nfjsonadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_nfjsonadapter_message">
		This is a demonstration of the NFJSONAdapter class, which is a full fledged adapter
		backed by a JSONArray.  Keep in mind, JSONArray is not part of a Collection and does not
		behave like a normal array.  It\'s ability to dynamically change the underlying data is
		limited but possible.\n
		\n
		If filtering is required, it\'s strongly recommended to use the JSONAdapter instead.
	</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - NFSparseAdapter-->
	<string name="info_nfsparseadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_nfsparseadapter_message">
		This is a demonstration of the NFSparseAdapter which, as the name suggests, is an adapter
		backed by a SparseArray.  It exposes most of the SparseArray methods with the key mapping to
		an adapter\'s row id and vice versa.  Keep in mind this behaves like a map, not a list.
		Putting to the adapter is not the same as adding to the adapter.\n
		\n
		This adapter does not support filtering and as a result contains no synchronized blocks
		which may help those worried about performance.  If filtering is required, it\'s strongly
		recommended to use the SparseAdapter instead.
	</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - RolodexArrayAdapter-->
	<string name="info_rolodex_arrayadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_rolodex_arrayadapter_message">
		<!--TODO: Implement-->
	</string>

	<!--Info Dialog - SparseAdapter-->
	<string name="info_sparseadapter_title">Adapter Demo Info</string>
	<string name="info_sparseadapter_message">
		This is a demonstration of the SparseAdapter which, as the name suggests, is an adapter
		backed by a SparseArray. It exposes most of the SparseArray methods with the key mapping to
		an adapter\'s row id and vice versa.  Keep in mind this behaves like a map, not a list.
		Putting to the adapter is not the same as adding to the adapter.\n
		\n
		This adapter supports filtering.  If filtering is not required, it\'s strongly recommended
		to use the NFSparseAdapter instead.
	</string>

	<!-- Info Dialog - JSONAdapter -->
	<string name="info_unittest_jsonadapter_title">Adapter Unit Test</string>
	<string name="info_unittest_jsonadapter_message">
		A quick and dirty setup to test various aspects of the JSONAdapter that doesn\'t quite fit
		with the normal presentable demo.
	</string>

	<!-- Info Dialog - NFJSONArrayAdapter -->
	<string name="info_unittest_nfjsonadapter_title">Adapter Unit Test</string>
	<string name="info_unittest_nfjsonadapter_message">
		A quick and dirty setup to test various aspects of the NFJSONAdapter that doesn\'t quite fit
		with the normal presentable demo.
	</string>
</resources>
